Guide to the Time Inc. Reference Files 1907-2015 (bulk 1933-2003) MS 3009-RG 3
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Reference Files
1907-2015 (bulk 1933-2003)
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 3
77 Linear feet in 19 document cases, 64 record cartons, 1 flat box, and 1 filing cabinet
The Time Inc. Reference Files document the the history of Time Inc. through overviews or historical summaries of various divisions and franchises. This record group originally may have been Time Inc.'s "central file." Materials include handbooks and manuals; runs of employee newsletters; seventy years of staff-wide memos; lists of department heads, correspondents, contributors, and subsidiaries; and records from various staff organizations.
Arrangement Note
Organized alphabetically based on Time Inc.'s original arrangement.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include privileged attorney correspondence; student records; medical records; personnel performance evaluations; contracts and agreements; and records with personally identifiable information. Unreformatted audiovisual material and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Restricted materials are located in box R6. Materials created within the past 35 years also may be subject to restriction on a case-by-case basis. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Reference Files document the history of various Time Inc. divisions such as the editing and publishing groups for the major titles, Circulation, various office locations, and Public Affairs; franchises such as the Sports Illustrated "Swimsuit Issue" and Time "Person of the Year" (originally "Man of the Year"); and staff organizations. Materials include press releases; handbooks and manuals; runs of employee newsletters and in-house organs, such as FYI and Keywords; seventy years of staff-wide memos; and lists of department heads, correspondents, contributors, and subsidiaries.
Specific items of interest in this collection include the Department Head Lists, which record the structure of the company and names and titles of top-level staff; and copies of FYI, an internal Time Inc. staff newsletter which discuss department and staffing changes, events and milestones, along with a card index of the contents.
While the Reference Files seem to serve a similar purpose to the Time Inc. Subject Files, this record group may have, at one point, been organically created by departments sending copies of informative records to Time Inc.'s "central file." It isn't clear which department had ownership of that file or who was allowed to access it. The creation of Reference Files or the central file may have changed over time.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital copies of the Department Head Lists recording the structure of the company and the top-level staff are available in the N-YHS Digital Collections: Time, Inc. department head lists, 1949-1987.
Memorandums.; Lists (document genres); Handbooks; Files (document groupings); Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporations -- History; New York (N.Y.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Press releases.; Newsletters.; Rockefeller Center -- Buildings; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- Buildings; Time, inc. -- History; Luce, Henry, III, 1925-2005
- Administrative Services: Departmental Profiles (Offsite-box 498, Folder 1)
- Administrative Services: Messenger: 1990- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 2)
- Administrative Services: Misc. (Offsite-box 498, Folder 3)
- Administrative Services: Greentime News (Environmental Newsletter): 1992 (Offsite-box 498, Folder 4)
- Administrative Services: Staff Home Address Lists: 1990- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 5)
- Administrative Services: Messenger extra copies: 1990- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 6)
- Administrative Services: The Silent 'S': 1993- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 7)
- Administrative Services: The Silent 'S': Extra Copies: 1993- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 8)
- Administrative Services: Memorandums: 1992- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 9)
- Administrative Services: Organization Charts (Offsite-box 498, Folder 10)
- Administrative Services: Records Management Manual: 1990 (Offsite-box 498, Folder 11)
- Administrative Services: SPIP Memorandums: 1992- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 12)
- Administrative Services: Travel Department: Trip Tips: 1992- (Offsite-box 498, Folder 13)
- Advertising: General (Offsite-box 498, Folder 14)
- All You (Offsite-box 498, Folder 15)
- American Express Publishing Corp. (Offsite-box 498, Folder 16)
- American Renewal: Single Issues: 1981 (Offsite-box 498, Folder 17)
- American Television and Communications Corporation (Offsite-box 498, Folder 18-19)
- AOL: Misc.: 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 498, Folder 20-21)
- AOL: Misc.: 2003 (Offsite-box 498, Folder 22)
- AOL: Misc.: 2004 (Offsite-box 499, Folder 1)
- AOL Time Warner: Merger (Offsite-box 499, Folder 2)
- AOL Time Warner Foundation (Offsite-box 499, Folder 2-3)
- Arch Forum/House and Home (Offsite-box 499, Folder 4-5)
- Archives (Offsite-box 499, Folder 6-7)
- Art (Offsite-box 499, Folder 8)
- Asia Week (Offsite-box 499, Folder 9)
- Awards (Offsite-box 499, Folder 10-12)
- Awards: Heiskell (Offsite-box 499, Folder 13)
- Awards: Luce Awards (Offsite-box 499, Folder 14)
- Awards: President's and Luce (Offsite-box 499, Folder 15)
- Board of Directors (Offsite-box 499, Folder 16)
- Books about Time Inc.: Busch, Noel: Research (Offsite-box 499, Folder 17)
- Books about Time Inc.: Busch, Noel: Misc. (Offsite-box 499, Folder 18)
- Book of the Month (Offsite-box 499-500)
- Books about Time Inc.: Byron: The Fanciest Dive (Offsite-box 500, Folder 2)
- Books about Time Inc.: Clurman, Richard M.: To The End of Time (Offsite-box 500, Folder 3)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume I: Distribution (Offsite-box 500)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume I: Distribution [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Atheneum (Offsite-box 500, Folder 5)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume I: Misc. (Offsite-box 500, Folder 6)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume I: Thank you letters (Offsite-box 500, Folder 9)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume II: Distribution Lists (Offsite-box 500, Folder 10-11)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume II: Distribution Misc. (Offsite-box 500, Folder 12)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume II: First Draft: Chapters 1-27, 1969 (Offsite-box 4095, Folder 1-7)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume II: Thank you letters (Offsite-box 500, Folder 13)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume II: Misc. (Offsite-box 500, Folder 14)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Atheneum Contract (Offsite-box 500)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Atheneum Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Drafts: Prologue et cetera, 1985 (Offsite-box 4096, Folder 1)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Drafts: Chapter 1-12, 1985 (Offsite-box 4096, Folder 2)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Drafts: Chapter 13-31, 1985 (Offsite-box 4097, Folder 1-19)
- Books about Time Inc.: Elson's History: Volume III: Complete Draft, 1985 (Offsite-box 4098, Folder 1-2)
- Books about Time Inc.: Hamblin, Dora J.: That Was The Life (Offsite-box 500, Folder 16)
- Books about Time Inc.: Herzstein, Robert: Henry R. Luce (Offsite-box 500, Folder 17)
- Books about Time Inc.: Hodgins, Eric: Time Was When (Offsite-box 500, Folder 18)
- Books about Time Inc.: Hodgins, Eric: Research (Offsite-box 500, Folder 19)
- Books about Time Inc.: Hodgins, Eric: Misc. (Offsite-box 500, Folder 20)
- Books about Time Inc.: Jessup, John: Ideas of Henry Luce (Offsite-box 500, Folder 21)
- Books about Time Inc.: Kraminov, Dan: Amur and the Turtle (Offsite-box 500, Folder 22)
- Books about Time Inc.: Martin, Ralph G.: Henry and Clare- An Intimate Portrait of the Luces (Offsite-box 500, Folder 23)
- Books about Time Inc.: Oberdorfer, Don: Tet! (Offsite-box 500, Folder 24)
- Books about Time Inc.: Prendergast's History (Offsite-box 500, Folder 25)
- Books about Time Inc.: Swanberg, William (Offsite-box 500, Folder 26)
- Books about Time Inc.: Wainwright, L. (Offsite-box 500, Folder 27)
- Books about Time Inc.: Wilner, Isaiah: Briton Hadden biography: The Man Time Forgot (Offsite-box 500, Folder 28)
- Books about Time Inc. (Offsite-box 501, Folder 1-2)
- Books and Arts Associates (Offsite-box 501, Folder 3-4)
- Books: Fortune (Offsite-box 501, Folder 5)
- Books by Time Incers (Offsite-box 501, Folder 6-7)
- Books Group (Offsite-box 501, Folder 8)
- Books: Misc. (Offsite-box 501, Folder 9)
- Books: Sports Illustrated (Offsite-box 501, Folder 10)
- Books: Sports Illustrated for Kids (Offsite-box 501, Folder 11)
- Books: Time (Offsite-box 501, Folder 12)
- Business 2.0: Misc. (Offsite-box 501, Folder 13)
- Cable News Network/CNN (Offsite-box 501, Folder 14-15)
- Cable TV: General (Offsite-box 501, Folder 16)
- Castle Rock Films (Offsite-box 501, Folder 17)
- Casualties: Time Inc. (Offsite-box 501, Folder 18)
- Circulation: General (Offsite-box 501, Folder 19-20)
- Circulation: International: 1950-1966 (Offsite-box 501, Folder 21-22)
- Circulation: International: 1932-1949 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 1)
- Circulation: International: 1967 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 2)
- Circulation: International: Print Order Summaries (Offsite-box 502, Folder 3)
- Circulation: International: Time Air Express: Print Order Summaries: 1941-1946 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 4)
- Circulation: Military (Offsite-box 502, Folder 5)
- Circulation Promotion: Inside Time: 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 6)
- Coastal Living (Offsite-box 502, Folder 7)
- Company Services: Communications (Offsite-box 502, Folder 8)
- Company Services: Reception (Offsite-box 502, Folder 9)
- Company Services: Misc. (Offsite-box 502, Folder 10)
- Comptroller's Department (Offsite-box 502, Folder 11)
- Constitution: A Quarterly Journal of the Foundation for the U.S. Constitution: Misc.: 1988-1995 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 18)
- Constitution: A Quarterly Journal of the Foundation for the U.S. Constitution: Vol 1/No. 1, Fall 1988: Prepub dummy and first issue (Offsite-box 502, Folder 19)
- Consumer Marketing (Offsite-box 502, Folder 12)
- Cooking Light (Offsite-box 502, Folder 20)
- Copy Acceptance (Offsite-box 502, Folder 13)
- Corporate: General: 1923-1955 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 21-22)
- Corporate: General: 1956-1959 (Offsite-box 502, Folder 23)
- Corporate: General: 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 502-503)
- Corporate: General: 1964-1975 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 2-4)
- Corporate: General: 1976-1986 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 4-5)
- Corporate: General: 1987 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 6)
- Corporate: General: Discussion of Corporate Strategy: June 1988 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 7)
- Corporate: General: Time Inc.: 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 8-9)
- Corporate: General: Time Warner Inc.: 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 10)
- Corporate: General: Time Warner Inc.: 1992-2000 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 11-12)
- Corporate: General: AOL Time Warner Inc.: Merger: 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 503, Folder 13-14)
- Corporate: General: AOL Time Warner Inc.: Jan.-June 2002 (Offsite-box 508, Folder 1)
- Corporate: General: AOL Time Warner Inc.: July-Dec. 2002 (Offsite-box 508, Folder 2-3)
- Corporate: General: AOL Time Warner Inc.: Jan.-Sept. 2003 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 1-2)
- Corporate: General: Time Warner: Oct.-Dec. 2003 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 3)
- Corporate: General: Time Warner: 2004 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 4)
- Corporate: General: AOLTime Warner: Accounting (Offsite-box 507, Folder 5)
- Corporate: General: Time Warner Name Change: Press Clips (Offsite-box 507, Folder 6)
- Corporate: Magazine: Circulation and rate trends: 1940-1967 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 7)
- Corporate: Manufacturing and distribution: Donnelley (Offsite-box 507, Folder 8)
- Corporate: Manufacturing and distribution: Misc. (Offsite-box 507, Folder 9-10)
- Corporate: Mission statements (Offsite-box 507, Folder 11)
- Corporate: Corporate philanthropy (Offsite-box 507, Folder 12-13)
- Corporate: Publicity: 1982 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 14)
- Corporate: Quarterly statements: 2000-2003 (Offsite-box 507, Folder 15-16)
- Corporate: Statements of Ownership (Offsite-box 508, Folder 11)
- Corporate Affairs: Edit: Lunches, Dinners, Etc (Offsite-box 502, Folder 14)
- Corporate Affairs: General (Offsite-box 502, Folder 15)
- Corporate Development (Offsite-box 502, Folder 16)
- Corporate Finance (Offsite-box 502, Folder 17)
- Corporate Secretary: Misc. (Offsite-box 507, Folder 17)
- Corporate Secretary: Stock (Offsite-box 507, Folder 18)
- Corporate Secretary: Stock (Offsite-box 508, Folder 4)
- Corporate Secretary: Stock Investment Analyses (Offsite-box 508, Folder 5)
- Corporate Secretary: Stockholders (Offsite-box 508, Folder 6-7)
- Corporate Secretary: Stockholders: Proxy Statement (Offsite-box 508, Folder 8-9)
- Corporate Secretary: Document Books: Archive's Safe (Offsite-box 508, Folder 10)
- Cottage Living: Southern Progress title: 2003- (Offsite-box 508, Folder 12)
- Dancyu (Offsite-box 508, Folder 13)
- Discover: Marked Index: Oct. 1980-April 1987 (Offsite-box 508, Folder 14-15)
- Discover: Misc. (Offsite-box 508, Folder 16)
- eCompany Now: Misc.: 2000- (Offsite-box 508, Folder 17)
- Edit: Church and State (Offsite-box 508, Folder 18-19)
- Edit: Lunches and Meetings: 1960 and Before (Offsite-box 509, Folder 1)
- Edit: Lunches and Meetings: 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 509, Folder 2)
- Edit: Lunches and Meetings: 1971 and After (Offsite-box 509, Folder 3)
- Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 509, Folder 4)
- Edit: Post-War Department: Early to Mid-1940s (Offsite-box 509, Folder 5)
- Edit: Researchers (Offsite-box 509, Folder 6-7)
- Editorial and Manufacturing Technology (Offsite-box 509, Folder 8)
- Edit: Services (Offsite-box 510, Folder 6)
- Editorial Services: Misc. (Offsite-box 509, Folder 9)
- Editorial Services: Edit Ref.: Manuals (Offsite-box 509, Folder 10-11)
- Edit: Services: Edit Ref.: Reports (Offsite-box 509, Folder 12)
- Edit: Ref.: Presentation background memos and drafts: April 1967 (Offsite-box 509, Folder 13)
- Editorial Services: Edit Ref. and Research Center Photos: Misc (Offsite-box 510, Folder 7-8)
- Editorial Services: Edit Ref.: Morgue and Library: Misc.: 1936-1996 (Offsite-box 509, Folder 16-17)
- Editorial Services: Misc. (Offsite-box 510, Folder 6)
- Editorial Services: Photo Lab (Offsite-box 509, Folder 18-19)
- Editorial Services: Picture Collection (Offsite-box 510, Folder 1)
- Editorial Services: Picture Collection: Doak Presentation: 2005 (Offsite-box 510, Folder 2)
- Editorial Services: Research Center: Publications (Offsite-box 510, Folder 3-4)
- Editorial Services: Warhol Lawsuit (Offsite-box 510, Folder 5)
- Editorial Services: Research Center: Misc (Offsite-box 510, Folder 9-10)
- Education Department (Offsite-box 510, Folder 11)
- Elle Japon: Misc. (Offsite-box 510, Folder 12)
- Emerge (Offsite-box 510, Folder 13)
- Employee Bookstore (Offsite-box 510, Folder 14)
- Entertainment Weekly: Advertising Rate Cards (Offsite-box 510, Folder 15)
- Entertainment Weekly: Meigher letter "To The Staff" only (Offsite-box 510, Folder 16)
- Entertainment Weekly: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 510, Folder 17)
- Entertainment Weekly: Lists (Offsite-box 510, Folder 18)
- Entertainment Weekly: Misc. (Offsite-box 510, Folder 19-20)
- Essence (Offsite-box 510, Folder 21)
- Family Life (Offsite-box 510, Folder 22)
- Field and Stream: 2000- (Offsite-box 510, Folder 23)
- Films: Time Inc. (Offsite-box 511, Folder 1)
- Filmstrips (Offsite-box 511, Folder 2)
- Finance: Memoranda: 1992- (Offsite-box 511, Folder 3)
- Financial: General (Offsite-box 511, Folder 4-5)
- Fortune: ABC Statements: 1930-1949 (Offsite-box 511, Folder 6)
- Fortune: ABC Statements: 1950-1964 (Offsite-box 511, Folder 7)
- Fortune: ABC Statements: Misc. (Offsite-box 511, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising: Lists: Index (Offsite-box 511, Folder 8)
- Fortune: Advertising: Rate Cards (Offsite-box 511, Folder 9-10)
- Fortune: 540 Book (Offsite-box 511, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Art (Offsite-box 511, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Business Hall of Fame (Offsite-box 511, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 511, Folder 15)
- Fortune: Edit: Misc. (Offsite-box 511, Folder 16)
- Fortune: Edit: Futures Notebook from Bob Lubar's files: Late 1950s (Offsite-box 511, Folder 17)
- Fortune: Edit: Market value of old issues (Offsite-box 511, Folder 18)
- Fortune: Edit: Supplements (Offsite-box 511, Folder 19)
- Fortune: Edit: Story of a Fortune Story (Offsite-box 511, Folder 20)
- Fortune Five Hundred (Offsite-box 512, Folder 1-2)
- Fortune Five Hundred: Supplement Copies 1, 2, and 3: 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 512, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Fortune Group (Offsite-box 512, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Fortune Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 512, Folder 5)
- Fortune: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 512, Folder 6)
- Fortune: History (Offsite-box 512, Folder 7-8)
- Fortune: History: Timeline and reminiscences (Offsite-box 512, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Index: 1930-1973 (incomplete) (Offsite-box 512, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Misc. (Offsite-box 512, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Production (Offsite-box 512, Folder 12)
- Fortune: U.S. Press: 1930-1949 (Offsite-box 512, Folder 13)
- Fortune: U.S. Press: 1960s (Offsite-box 512, Folder 14)
- Fortune: U.S. Press: 1989 (Offsite-box 512, Folder 15)
- Fortune: International: Misc. (Offsite-box 512, Folder 16)
- Fortune: Small Business (Offsite-box 512, Folder 17)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: A-By (Drawer 1)
  Scope and Contents Note
  FYI is an internal Time Inc. staff newsletter. The index cards contain names and subjects mentioned within the newsletter up through 2000. In 2002, Time Inc. began distributing the newsletter online. Along with the date of the FYI issue, the card may include a brief description of the article. The majority of index cards are for staff members. Also included are article subjects (banks, Dracula, hurricanes, journalim careers, lunch guide, military absentees, novels about Time Inc., running, typing contest); Time Inc. departments (Human Resources, Lecturers' Bureau, Letters to the Editor); and Time Inc. events (lease renewals of building, retirements, rubber tree arrives at Reception Center, TV filming at the Time and Life Building). There are also large sections for the Exhibition Center, Fortune, Life, March of Time, News Service, Sports Illustrated, Time, Time Inc., and Time-Life.
  The index may not be in exact alphabetical order due to years of use.
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: C-D (Drawer 2)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: E-G (Drawer 3)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: H-J (Drawer 4)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: K-Ly (Drawer 5)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: Ma-N (Drawer 6)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: O-R (Drawer 7)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: Sa-Sz (Drawer 8)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet:T-V (Drawer 9)
- FYI: Index Card Cabinet: W-Z (Drawer 10)
- FYI: Issues: 1935-1940 (Box 526)
- FYI: Issues: 1940-1941 (Box 527)
- FYI: Issues: 1941 (Box 527A)
- FYI: Issues: 1941-1942 (Box 528)
- FYI: Issues: 1942-1945 (Box 529)
- FYI: Issues: 1942-1945 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- FYI: Issues: 1945-1948 (Box 530)
- FYI: Issues: 1948-1952 (Box 531)
- FYI: Issues: 1953-1957 (Box 532)
- FYI: Issues: 1957-1961 (Box 533)
- FYI: Issues: 1962-1965 (Box 534)
- FYI: Issues: 1965-1968 (Box 535)
- FYI: Issues: 1968-1971 (Box 536)
- FYI: Issues: 1972-1985 (Box 537)
- FYI: Issues: 1986-1992 (Box 538)
- FYI: Issues: 1993-1996 (Box 539)
- FYI: Issues: 1997-2001 (Box 540)
- FYI: Issues: 2002 (Box 541, Folder 1)
- FYI Online: Issues: 2002-2005 (Box 541, Folder 2-5)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1943 (Box 541, Folder 6-7)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 542)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 549, Folder 1-15)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1956 (Offsite-box 549, Folder 16)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 550)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 551)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 552)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 553)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 554)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1979 (Offsite-box 863, Folder 5-8)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 555)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 556)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1988-1998 (Offsite-box 557)
- FYI: Duplicate issues: 1999-2004 (Offsite-box 558, Folder 1-5)
- FYI: Calendars: 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 558, Folder 6)
- FYI: Calendars: 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 558, Folder 7)
- FYI: Scrapbook (Offsite-box 558, Folder 13)
- FYI: Documentation: 55th Anniversary Issue w/ FYI Timeline: 4/24/95 (Offsite-box 558, Folder 8)
- FYI: Documentation: Batman Comic: 1992 (Offsite-box 558, Folder 9)
- FYI: Documentation: Misc. (Offsite-box 558, Folder 10)
- FYI: Documentation: New Research Center Cover (Offsite-box 558, Folder 11)
- FYI: Documentation: Style and Permissions (Offsite-box 558)
- FYI: Documentation: Style and Permissions [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- General Learning: Misc. (Offsite-box 512, Folder 18)
- General Learning: Press Releases (Offsite-box 512, Folder 19)
- Golf: 2000- (Offsite-box 512, Folder 20)
- Grupo Editorial Expansion (Offsite-box 512, Folder 21)
- Health Publishing Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 512, Folder 22)
- Home Box Office: History: J Barrington mss.: First ten years (Offsite-box 512, Folder 23)
- Home Box Office: Misc.: 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 512)
- Home Box Office: Misc.: 1970-1980 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Home Box Office: Misc.: 1981-1990 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 1)
- Home Box Office: Misc.: 1991-2000 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 2-3)
- Home Box Office: Misc.: 2001- (Offsite-box 513, Folder 4)
- Home Box Office: Press Releases (Offsite-box 513, Folder 5)
- Home Office (Offsite-box 513, Folder 6)
- hotdots (Offsite-box 513, Folder 7)
- House and Home: Index (Offsite-box 513, Folder 8)
- i.e.: Time Warner Newsletter: First Issue: Spring 1992 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 9-10)
  The final issue as i.e. was published November/December 1997. This newsletter was renamed TWX as of January 1998.
- i.e.: 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 11-12)
- i.e.: 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 13-14)
- i.e.: Misc. (Offsite-box 513, Folder 15)
- Imitations of Time Inc. magazines (Offsite-box 513, Folder 16)
- Information Technology: 1981-2007 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 17)
- Information Technology: Memos from Tsufura, Lamarr; Zubarev, Alex: 2008 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 18)
- Information Technology: Memos from Tsufura, Lamarr; Zubarev, Alex: 2009 (Offsite-box 513, Folder 19)
- Inside Time Inc: 1984- (Offsite-box 514, Folder 1)
- Inside Time Inc.: First Issue: Summer 1984 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 2)
- Inside Time Inc.: Misc. (Offsite-box 514, Folder 3)
- InStyle: Advertising Rate Cards (Offsite-box 514, Folder 4)
- InStyle: Misc. (Offsite-box 514, Folder 5)
- International: Bannings: Lists (Offsite-box 514, Folder 6)
- International: Bannings: Misc. (Offsite-box 514, Folder 7)
- International: Operations Reports: 1943 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 8)
- International: Misc. (Offsite-box 514, Folder 9-11)
- International: Operations Reports: 1946 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 12-13)
- International: Operations Reports: 1943-1947 (Offsite-box 514, Folder 14)
- International: So We Went Abroad (Offsite-box 514, Folder 15)